Nilana Pereira Da Rocha

Interior Architect

https://nilanapereiradarocha.github.io/

457 Sponsorship Visa

20/14 Nerang Road, Cronulla, NSW, Australia nilanaarquitetura@gmail.com +61_412_420_435

PROFILE

Bachelor Degree in Architecture and Urban Design. With 4 years handling professional projects and improving my problem solving skills. I have had the responsibility of managing several projects utilising the use of my enthusiasm, creativity and dedication to achieve results.

Throughout my career, I have developed good communication and interpersonal skills. I have a very responsive personality and have the ability to work in a team. I am result oriented and I'm a responsible and punctual person.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Floral Designer: Fleur Events - Taren Point, NSW - AU - Oct 2017 - Mar 2018,

- → Developed floral decorations, predominantly artificial flowers, for events.
- → In loco decoration installs.
- → Stock management.
- Collaborated with team members and customer to achieve the expected decoration.

Reference: Sophie Smith - Manager of Fleur Events. Phone: +61 401 580 780

Interior Designer, N A Projetos e Decorações LTDA - Rio Vermelho Salvador- BA, Brazil - Dec 2011 - Dec 2015

- → Created and detailed designs using AutoCAD
- → Collaborated closely with stakeholders analyzing and understanding their requirements.
- Brainstormed with technical and sales teams to better accommodate future client needs.

Achievement

Participated in several commercial and residential interior design and architecture projects, and projects such as Fecomércio-BA architecture project: https://nilanarocha.github.io/fecomercio-ba/

AutoCAD Drafter- Residential/Sales Consultant e-CONSTRUIR Representação Cerâmica Cecrisa/Portinari - Lauro de Freitas-BA, Brazil - Jul 2011 — Dec 2011

- → Analyzed and understood client needs to offer the best options/solutions available.
- → Responded to product and service enquiries within the showroom, via phone or email;
- → Helped clients/customers with product selections based on their needs.
- → Organised and provided quotation for projects.

EDUCATION

- → Upper intermediate, SCE Sydney College of English Sydney, NSW, AU Jan-Aug 2017
- → Bachelor's Degree, Architecture and Urban Design União Metropolitana De Educação E Cultura, UNIME, Lauro de Freitas, BA, Brazil 2009-2015

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- → Revit (3D CAD)
 TAFE NSW Aug 2017 Sydney, NSW, AU
- → AutoCAD

Real & Dados - September 2011 - BA, Brazil

→ Microsoft Office

Real & Dados - January 2011- BA, Brazil